Contact

akabhatt999@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/aakash-bhatt-92960712a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Core Java

C++

HTML

Aakash Bhatt

Aspiring Data Scientist

Thane

Summary

Experienced Frontend Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in C++, ASP.NET MVC, Core Java, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), and Wordpress, and Shopify. Strong engineering professional with a Bsc-IT focused in Computer Software Engineering from Mumbai University Mumbai.

Experience

Impaq Technologies Pvt Ltd 11 months

Frontend Developer
June 2018 - April 2019 (11 months)
Mumbai Area, India

Converting Photoshop(PSD) files to Real World Websites using HTML5, CSS3, BOOTSTRAP4 and maintain existing projects

Frontend Developer August 2018 - August 2018 (1 month) Mumbai Area, India

Education

Great Learning

PGP-Data Science · (2019 - 2020)

Mumbai University Mumbai

Bsc-IT, Computer Software Engineering · (2015 - 2018)